<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Site-infos on RHElements</title>
    <link>/site-info/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Site-infos on RHElements</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 14:02:31 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/site-info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Join the Community</title>
      <link>/site-info/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 14:02:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/site-info/community/</guid>
      <description>Contribute to RHElements How to Report a Bug Think you found a bug? Please check the list of open issues to see if your bug has already been reported. If it hasn&amp;rsquo;t please submit a new issue.
How to Suggest a Feature or Enhancement Open an issue which describes the feature you would like to see, why you want it, how it should work, etc.
Bootstrapping Your Local Development Environment npm install  Running Tests npm test  Code of Conduct This project is governed by the Contributor Covenant Code of Conduct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of conduct</title>
      <link>/site-info/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 14:02:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/site-info/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Contributor Covenant Code of Conduct Our Pledge In the interest of fostering an open and welcoming environment, we as contributors and maintainers pledge to making participation in our project and our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body size, disability, ethnicity, gender identity and expression, level of experience, nationality, personal appearance, race, religion, or sexual identity and orientation.
Our Standards Examples of behavior that contributes to creating a positive environment include:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Help</title>
      <link>/site-info/get-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 14:02:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/site-info/get-help/</guid>
      <description>Reach out to the team Drop us a line at rhelements@redhat.com</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>